The Call is a horror, thriller film directed by Timothy Woodward Jr..
In the fall of 1987, a group of small-town friends must survive the night in
the home of a sinister couple after a tragic accident occurs.
Needing only to make a single phone call, the request seems horribly ordinary
until they realize that this call could change their life…or end it.
Edith Cranston, played by Lin Shaye.
Edward Cranston, played by Tobin Bell.
Chris, played by Chester Rushing.
Tonya, played by Erin Sanders.
Harliss, played by Judd Lormand.
Zack, played by Mike C. Manning.
The Call of the Wild is a 2020 American adventure film directed by
Chris Sanders from a screenplay by Michael Green.
It is based on the 1903 novel of the same name by Jack London.
The film stars Harrison Ford, Omar Sy, Cara Gee, Dan
Stevens, Karen Gillan, and Bradley Whitford.
Set during the 1890s Klondike Gold Rush, the film follows a dog named Buck as he is stolen from his home in
California and sent to the Yukon, where he befriends an old outdoorsman and begins a life-altering adventure.
The Call of the Wild was released in the United States on February 21, 2020, by
20th Century Studios (its first film under the company's new name).
It received mixed-to-positive reviews from critics, who praised Ford's performance, John Powell’s music and the
"entertaining action and earnest tone" but criticized the "uncanny valley" effect of the CGI animals.
The film's release was cut short due to the COVID-19 pandemic, grossing $111.1 million against a
production budget of $125–150 million, and lost the studio an estimated $50–100 million.
The film explores themes of missing child, phone call, 1980s.
The tone is dark and intense.